<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Happy Dev]]></title><description><![CDATA[Blog to pen down my thoughts about development etc..]]></description><link>https://mdsaleemj.github.io/blog/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 07:08:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Yet Another Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is an yet another blog post and i am bored to write this. The purpose of this blog is to create a new blog/portfolio for me and…]]></description><link>https://mdsaleemj.github.io/blog//third-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://mdsaleemj.github.io/blog//third-post/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is an yet another blog post and i am bored to write this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this blog is to create a new blog/portfolio for me and learning my website building skills using GatsbyJS. I love Gatsby for the speed and productivity when building websites.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reactjs to Gatsbyjs !]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gatsby made developing website possible using React stack. I couldn't imagine how React which started as perfect tool for developing SPA…]]></description><link>https://mdsaleemj.github.io/blog//reactjs-to-gatsby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://mdsaleemj.github.io/blog//reactjs-to-gatsby/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 23:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Gatsby made developing website possible using React stack. I couldn&apos;t imagine how React which started as perfect tool for developing SPA ( when Angular 1 started well but failed miserably) and integrated well with supporting tools(like Webpack, Babel, CSS in JS libraries) and now in the land of developing websites , it has received outstanding ovation. It&apos;s actually React which helped developers to migrate to ES6 related features very easily.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; React community popularized the usage of ES6 in the last few years for old/new Javascript developers. Thank You ReactJS community for giving such a wonderful thing .&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Thank You Gatsby for taking this forward and giving back to community , a real super easy way for developing websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Dev&lt;br/&gt;
Saleem&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My First Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is first blog post and i am excited. The purpose of this blog is to create a new blog/portfolio for me and learning my website building…]]></description><link>https://mdsaleemj.github.io/blog//first-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://mdsaleemj.github.io/blog//first-post/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is first blog post and i am excited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this blog is to create a new blog/portfolio for me and learning my website building skills using GatsbyJS. I love Gatsby for the speed and productivity when building websites.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>